Arcadio Díaz Quiñones Papers, circa 1944-2019 (bulk 1970-2012 ): Finding Aid
Princeton University Library. Special Collections.
- Series 2: Correspondence, 1959-2019; 17 boxes (1 partial) 2 items
  - AM 2007-4; AM 2016-95; AM 2017-33; AM 2017-99; 2019-114, 1959-2019; 7 boxes (1 partial)
    - Colomer, Josep, 1997; 1 box (partial)
    - Colón-Santana, José Enrique, 2014; 1 box (partial)
    - Coloquio - Berlin, 1995; 1 box (partial)
    - Coloquio - El Caribe entre imperios, 1994; 1 box (partial)
    - Coloquio - Erlangen (Alemania), 1997; 1 box (partial)
    - Coloquio - Estudios Culturales - Bogotá, 1997; 1 box (partial)
    - Coloquio - Historia de los intelectuales (Universidad Nacional de Quilmes), 2006; 1 box (partial)
    - Coloquio - New York University, 1997; 1 box (partial)
    - Coloquio - Revistas Académicas (Puerto Rico), 2000; 1 box (partial)
    - Coloquium - Cuba, 1995; 1 box (partial)
    - Coloquium - Dartmonth University, 1995; 1 box (partial)
    - Coloquium - La literatura después de Borges, 2000; 1 box (partial)
    - Coloquium - Puerto Ricans: second class citizens?, 2001; 1 box (partial)
    - Concepción, Alma, 1998, 2016; 1 box (partial)
    - Concepción, Carmen Clacso, 2007; 1 box (partial)
    - Concha, Jaime, circa 1984; 1 box (partial)
    - Congreso - Universidad Nacional de la Plata (Argentina), 2009; 1 box (partial)
    - Consejo Superior de Investigaciones Científicas (Madrid), 2001; 1 box (partial)
    - Congreso de la nueva narrativa Hispanoamericana (Cali, Colombia), 1974; 1 box (partial)
    - Consulado General de España, 1997; 1 box (partial)
    - Coombs, Douglas, 2006; 1 box (partial)
    - Cordero, Ernesto, undated; 1 box (partial)
    - Cortés Cabán, David (NYC), circa 2002, 2008; 1 box (partial)
    - Costa, Carmen Mí (y Tony Ramos Mattei) - Puerto Rico, 1987; 1 box (partial)
    - Cotto Morales, Liliana (Puerto Rico), undated; 1 box (partial)
    - Cox-Alomar, Rafael, circa 1996-2000s; 1 box (partial)
    - Cruz Rodríguez, Nelly (Puerto Rico), 2000; 1 box (partial)
    - Cubano Iguina, Astrid, 1996; 1 box (partial)
    - CUNY City College, N.Y., 2012; 1 box (partial)
    - CUNY - Graduate Center, 1977; 1 box (partial)
    - Cupeles, Juan David, 2001; 1 box (partial)
    - Curbelo, Irene (Puerto Rico), 1997; 1 box (partial)
    - Cushman, Keith, 1990; 1 box (partial)
    - Cutler, Kit, 2004; 1 box (partial)
    - Dartmouth College coloquio, circa 1988-1989; 1 box (partial)
    - Davis, Natalie, 1991, 2019; 1 box (partial)
    - Dávila, Angela María, undated; 1 box (partial)
    - De Armas, Emilio (Cuba), 1991; 1 box (partial)
    - De Toro, Alfonso, 2002; 1 box (partial)
    - Del Risco, Enrique (Cuba), undated; 1 box (partial)
    - Delano, Jack, 1982; 1 box (partial)
    - Dembowski, Peter, 1983; 1 box (partial)
    - Di Tella, Andrés (Argentina - Festival de Documentales), circa 2002; 1 box (partial)
    - Diálogo - Universidad de Puerto Rico - Luis Fernando Coss, circa 1991; 1 box (partial)
    - Díaz, Alicia, circa 1998-2018; 1 box (partial)
    - Díaz, Edith (my sister), 2010, 2018; 1 box (partial)
    - Díaz, Junot, circa 2005; 1 box (partial)
    - Djuric, Dusan, circa 2009; 1 box (partial)
    - Dominguez, Wilfredo (Cuba), undated; 1 box (partial)
    - Dorfman, Ariel, circa 1986; 1 box (partial)
    - Duchesne Winter, Juan, 2002; 1 box (partial)
    - Droz, Vanessa, 2015; 1 box (partial)
    - Duquella, Maud, 2005; 1 box (partial)
    - East, Harlem, 2015; 1 box (partial)
    - Echavarría, Arturo (Puerto Rico), circa 1991-1993; 1 box (partial)
    - Echeverría, Pablo, 2016; 1 box (partial)
    - Ediciones Callejón, circa 1999-2008; 1 box (partial)
    - Ediciones Cátedra, 2000; 1 box (partial)
    - Ediciones Huracán (Puerto Rico), circa 1980s-1993; 1 box (partial)
    - Ediciones RIALP (Spain), 1991; 1 box (partial)
    - Ediciones SM (Puerto Rico), 2011, 2015; 1 box (partial)
    - Ediciones Santillana (Puerto Rico), 1997, 2006, 2011; 1 box (partial)
    - Editorial - Companhia Das Letras (Brasil), 2016; 1 box (partial)
    - Editorial de la Universidad de Puerto Rico, 2001; 1 box (partial)
    - Editorial Universidad Nacional de Quilmes, circa 2006; 1 box (partial)
    - El Colegio de México, 2005; 1 box (partial)
    - El País (Madrid), 1998; 1 box (partial)
    - Elliott, John, 1989-1990; 1 box (partial)
    - Ellrich, Robert, 1988; 1 box (partial)
    - Esquilín, Mary Ann Gosser, 1991; 1 box (partial)
    - Estrade, Paul, 1986; 1 box (partial)
    - Fetcher, Alan, 1992; 1 box (partial)
    - Fernández, James, circa 1990s; 1 box (partial)
    - Fernández, Harold, circa 1980s; 1 box (partial)
    - Fernández Bravo, Alvaro, circa 1990s; 1 box (partial)
    - Fernández Bravo, Alvaro (Argentina) y Florencia Garramuño, circa 2006, 2013; 1 box (partial)
    - Fernández Olmos, Margarite, 1997; 1 box (partial)
    - Ferrari, León (Argentina), circa 1986; 1 box (partial)
    - Ferré, Maurice A., 2006; 1 box (partial)
    - Ferré, Rosario, circa 1986; 1 box (partial)
    - Ferrer, Rafael, circa 2012; 1 box (partial)
    - Fideicomiso Conservación (Puerto Rico), 2005; 1 box (partial)
    - Firbas, Paul, 1998; 1 box (partial)
    - Fleischmann, Ulrich, circa 1994-1995; 1 box (partial)
    - Flores, Juan, circa 1995-1996, 2014; 1 box (partial)
    - Flores, René C., circa 1987; 1 box (partial)
    - Fordham University, 1983; 1 box (partial)
    - Fowler, Victor, circa 1994; 1 box (partial)
    - Fradera, Josep (Barcelona), circa 1986-2006; 1 box (partial)
    - Franco, Jean, 2000; 1 box (partial)
    - Frauenheim, Edward, circa 1988; 1 box (partial)
    - Fromm, Georg, 1993-1994; 1 box (partial)
    - Fuentes, Alfonso (Puerto Rico), 2018; 1 box (partial)
    - Fundación Nilita, Vientós Gastón - Nieves Falcón, Luis, 2007; 1 box (partial)
    - Fundación Puertorriqueña de las Humanidades, circa 2010s; 1 box (partial)
    - Funes, Fernan (Cuba), 2005; 1 box (partial)
    - Funes, Patricia (Argentina), 1993; 1 box (partial)
    - Funes, Reinaldo (Cuba), 1994; 1 box (partial)
    - Funes, Reinaldo and Deborah, circa 1990s; 1 box (partial)
    - Gallo, Rubén, circa 2002; 1 box (partial)
    - Gandini, Gerardo, 1998; 1 box (partial)
    - Gandolfi, Laura, 2013; 1 box (partial)
    - García, Gervasio L., circa 1974-2016; 1 box (partial)
    - García, José Miguel, 1963-1964; 1 box (partial)
    - García Canclini, Nestor, circa 1984-1985; 1 box (partial)
    - García-Castro, José Miguel (Puerto Rico), 2002; 1 box (partial)
    - García Passalacqua, Juan Manuel (Puerto Rico), circa 1981; 1 box (partial)
    - García-Ramis, Magali, 2015; 1 box (partial)
    - García-Romen, José (France), 2001; 1 box (partial)
    - Garramuño, Carlos (Argentina), undated; 1 box (partial)
    - Garramuño, Florencia, 1996; 1 box (partial)
    - Garvey, LouAnn (Princeton), circa 1982; 1 box (partial)
    - Geist, Anthony, 1983; 1 box (partial)
    - Gelpí, Juan (Puerto Rico), circa 1987-2000; 1 box (partial)
    - Generalitat de Catalunya, Coloquio, Barcelona, 1986; 1 box (partial)
    - Geyman, Matt, 1980; 1 box (partial)
    - Giberti, Eva, 1987; 1 box (partial)
    - Gilman, Claudia (Argentina), 1997; 1 box (partial)
    - Gilman, Stephen, undated; 1 box (partial)
    - Glantz, Margo, circa 1990s-2009; 1 box (partial)
    - Gledson, John, 1989-1990; 1 box (partial)
    - Godreau, Michel, circa 2001; 1 box (partial)
    - Gomez Asencio, José, circa 1987; 1 box (partial)
    - González, Eduardo, circa 1993; 1 box (partial)
    - González, Elena, 2003; 1 box (partial)
    - González, José Eduardo, 1997; 1 box (partial)
    - González, José Luis, circa 1976-1980s; 1 box (partial)
    - González, Lydia Milagros, 2002-2005; 1 box (partial)
    - González, Manuel (Madrid), 1985; 1 box (partial)
    - González, Patricia, 1985; 1 box (partial)
    - González, Ruben (Puerto Rico), circa 1976-1986; 1 box (partial)
    - González-Echevarría, Roberto, circa 1987-1989; 1 box (partial)
    - González López, Libia, 2009; 1 box (partial)
    - González Stephan, Beatriz, 1994; 1 box (partial)
    - González-Vales, Luis, 1998; 1 box (partial)
    - Gorelik, Adrián, 2003; 1 box (partial)
    - Gotay, Consuelo, circa 1980s-2005; 1 box (partial)
    - Gras, Dunia (Barcelona), circa 1990s-2012; 1 box (partial)
    - Guerrero, Gustavo, 2018; 1 box (partial)
    - Gunning, Robert (Princeton University), circa 1989-1991; 1 box (partial)
    - Gutiérrez Mouat, Ricardo, 1994; 1 box (partial)
    - Guzmán, Fernando (from prison), 1994; 1 box (partial)
    - Habibe, Henry (Curacao), circa 1980s; 1 box (partial)
    - Hall, Gwendolyn, 1990; 1 box (partial)
    - Harvard University, circa 1988-1992; 1 box (partial)
    - Henessy, Alistar (University of Warwick), circa 1987-1992; 1 box (partial)
    - Henríquez, Pedro (Chile), 1989, 2003; 1 box (partial)
    - Hermosilla, Andrés, circa 1995-1997; 1 box (partial)
    - Hernández, Carmen Dolores (Puerto Rico), 1998; 1 box (partial)
    - Hernández, Orlando, 2001, 2004; 1 box (partial)
    - Herrera, Ingrid, 1997; 1 box (partial)
    - Herrera, Juan Carlos (Cuba), 1994; 1 box (partial)
    - Herrera, María Cristina (Cuba), 1996; 1 box (partial)
    - Hidalgo, Cecilia (Buenos Aires), 1993; 1 box (partial)
    - Hirschman, Albert D., circa 1993-1994, 2013; 1 box (partial)
    - Hirschman, Sarah, 2009, 2012; 1 box (partial)
    - Hoffmann, François, 1986; 1 box (partial)
    - Holiday, David, 1994; 1 box (partial)
    - Hollander, Robert, undated; 1 box (partial)
    - Hollensteiner, Stephan, circa 1995; 1 box (partial)
    - Homar, Lorenzo, circa 1986-2015; 1 box (partial)
    - Homar, Susan, 2004; 1 box (partial)
    - Hostos Community College, circa 2007-2012; 1 box (partial)
    - Hostos Community College (Tercer Milenio), 1992-1994; 1 box (partial)
    - Hourcade, Eduardo, 1997; 1 box (partial)
    - Huerta, David (México), circa 1989-2014; 1 box (partial)
    - Hunter College, 1996, 2008; 1 box (partial)
    - Ichikawa, Emilio, 1995; 1 box (partial)
    - Irby, James, 1980; 1 box (partial)
    - Irizarry, Awilda, 1988; 1 box (partial)
    - Irizarry, Guillermo, circa 2005; 1 box (partial)
    - Izard, Miguel, 1987; 1 box (partial)
    - Jacobs, Bárbara (México), 1998; 1 box (partial)
    - Jaramillo Zuluaga, Eduardo, 1991; 1 box (partial)
    - James, Conrad, 2004; 1 box (partial)
    - Janney, Frank, 1989; 1 box (partial)
    - Jimenez, Michael F., circa 1980s-1990s; 1 box (partial)
    - Jitrik, Noé, circa 1993, 2014; 1 box (partial)
    - Julie, 1994; 1 box (partial)
    - Jusino-Campos, Edgardo, 1998; 1 box (partial)
    - Kauffman, Leslie, 1985; 1 box (partial)
    - Kenin, Aaron Leon, 1989, 1991; 1 box (partial)
    - La Tertulia (Puerto Rico), circa 1982-1983; 1 box (partial)
    - Lachambre, Michel, 1964; 1 box (partial)
    - Lagos-Pope, María-Inés, 1986; 1 box (partial)
    - Lamming, George, 2005; 1 box (partial)
    - Landreau, John, circa 1994; 1 box (partial)
    - Latin America Literary Review, 1997; 1 box (partial)
    - Latin American Legal Defense, 2013; 1 box (partial)
    - Latin American Studies Association (LASA), circa 1985-1997; 1 box (partial)
    - Lauder Institute (Wharton School), 1989; 1 box (partial)
    - Leader, Alexandra, circa 2004, 2019; 1 box (partial)
    - Leggett, Gary, 2002-2004; 1 box (partial)
    - Leenhardt, Jacques, 1988; 1 box (partial)
    - Lehigh University, 1995; 1 box (partial)
    - León, Luz E., 1971; 1 box (partial)
    - Lesser, Chris, 2006; 1 box (partial)
    - Levin, Elena and Harry, 1980; 1 box (partial)
    - Lewis, David E., 1992, 1994, 2013; 1 box (partial)
    - Lewis Galanes, Adriana, 1977; 1 box (partial)
    - Lima, Lázaro, 2012; 1 box (partial)
    - Lomnitz, Claudio, 2014; 1 box (partial)
    - Long, Mary, circa 2000s; 1 box (partial)
    - Long, Marx, 2002; 1 box (partial)
    - López, Pedro Miguel, 2010; 1 box (partial)
    - López Baralt, Luce, 1986; 1 box (partial)
    - López Baralt, Merce, circa 1990s; 1 box (partial)
    - López Ramírez, Tomás, 1986; 1 box (partial)
    - López Sobá, Elías, 1985; 1 box (partial)
    - Lozano, María, 1988; 1 box (partial)
    - Ludmer, Josefina, circa 1986-1987; 1 box (partial)
    - Lugo Ortiz, Agnes, 1992-1993; 1 box (partial)
    - Luis, Gordon & Sybil, 1985; 1 box (partial)
    - Luis, William, 1988; 1 box (partial)
    - Luna, Noel, circa 2000s-2018; 1 box (partial)
    - MacLeod, Murdo J., circa 1989; 1 box (partial)
    - Madero, Marta, circa 1987; 1 box (partial)
    - Maeseneer, Rita de, 2004; 1 box (partial)
    - Maldonado, Adal, 2002; 1 box (partial)
    - Maldonado, Alex (Puerto Rico), 1981; 1 box (partial)
    - Malkiel, Nancy, 1997; 1 box (partial)
    - Mancini, Nydia (Puerto Rico), 1999; 1 box (partial)
    - Manzoni, Celina, circa 1990s; 1 box (partial)
    - Marichal, Sylvia, 1979; 1 box (partial)
    - Marqués de Armas, Pedro (Cuba), 1998; 1 box (partial)
    - Marsh Kennerly, Catherine, circa 1999; 1 box (partial)
    - Martin Rodríguez, Manuel, 1998; 1 box (partial)
    - Martínez, José Miguel (Madrid), 1997; 1 box (partial)
    - Martínez, Tomás Eloy, circa 2010; 1 box (partial)
    - Martínez García, Pedro (Madrid), circa 1965-1966; 1 box (partial)
    - Martínez González, Carmen y Susana, 1985; 1 box (partial)
    - Martínez González del Campo, José Miguel, 1971; 1 box (partial)
    - Martínez Novo, Carmen (España), 1987; 1 box (partial)
    - Martorell, Antonio (Puerto Rico), circa 2000s; 1 box (partial)
    - Martorell, Antonio "Imagining Betances" Hunter College, 2004 March 29; 1 box (partial)
      Materials include 1 floppy disk (3.5"). Antonio Martorell's "Imagining Betances."
      For preservation reasons, original analog and digital media may not be read or played back in the reading room. Users may visually inspect physical media, but may not remove it from its enclosure. All analog audiovisual media must be digitized to preservation-quality standards prior to use. Patrons may request digital copies of original analog media, but will be responsible for the cost of digital conversion, payable in advance. Turn-around time for such requests will depend on the size and scope of the project. Requests should be directed to Public Services staff.
    - Marzán, Julio, 1983; 1 box (partial)
    - Masi, Perla, 2011; 1 box (partial)
    - Masiello, Francine, circa 1994; 1 box (partial)
    - Massachusetts Institute of Technology (MIT), 2005-2006; 1 box (partial)
    - Matilla Rivas, Alfredo (Puerto Rico), 1988; 1 box (partial)
    - Matos Rodríguez, Félix, 1983; 1 box (partial)
    - Mayoral, Roberto, circa 1988-1989; 1 box (partial)
    - Mazzotti, José Antonio, 1993; 1 box (partial)
    - McCook, Stuart, 1993-1994; 1 box (partial)
    - Meira Monteiro, Pedro, 2002, 2006; 1 box (partial)
    - Mellon Foundation, 1990; 1 box (partial)
    - Mellon/Clacso, 1988; 1 box (partial)
    - Melgar, Lucía, 2004, 2011; 1 box (partial)
    - Mena, Miguel D. (Dominican Republic), 1994; 1 box (partial)
    - Méndez-Clark, Ronald, 1983, 1992; 1 box (partial)
    - Méndez Rodenas, Adriana, 1998; 1 box (partial)
    - Menjivar, Stacey, 2018; 1 box (partial)
    - Merrim, Stephanie, circa 1986-1987; 1 box (partial)
    - Millones, Luis, circa 1988-1990s; 1 box (partial)
    - Mintz, Sidney, 1985-1986, 1997; 1 box (partial)
    - Miranda Roberto, circa 1977-1982; 1 box (partial)
    - Molloy, Sylvia, circa 1980s; 1 box (partial)
    - Monsiváis, Carlos (México), circa 1985-1986; 1 box (partial)
    - Montaldo, Graciela, circa 1996; 1 box (partial)
    - Montclair State University Colloquium, circa 1998; 1 box (partial)
    - Montero, Oscar, circa 1984-2003; 1 box (partial)
    - Mora, Gabriela, 1987, 2016; 1 box (partial)
    - Morales, Jorge A. (Puerto Rico), 2019; 1 box (partial)
    - Morell, Hortensia, 2013; 1 box (partial)
    - Moreno-Fraginals, Manuel, circa 1990s; 1 box (partial)
    - Morr, Heather, 2007; 1 box (partial)
    - Morrison, Toni, 1988; 1 box (partial)
      Contains paper by Toni Morrison Unspeakable Things Unspoken: The Afro-American Presence in American Literature. Dedicated to Díaz Quiñones and signed by author.
    - Morse, Richard, 1987, 1993; 1 box (partial)
    - Mozo, Emilio, 1983; 1 box (partial)
    - Muller-Bergh, Klaus, circa 1996; 1 box (partial)
    - Muñiz, Benjamin, 1987, 1993; 1 box (partial)
    - Muñoz Millanes, José, circa 1987; 1 box (partial)
    - Murthy, Raghu, circa 1980s-1990; 1 box (partial)
    - National Tsing Huan University, 1993; 1 box (partial)
    - Navarra, Gilda, undated; 1 box (partial)
    - New York University, circa 1998-2001; 1 box (partial)
    - Newark Public Library (Puerto Rico, 1898-1998), 1 box (partial)
    - Nicot, José (Princeton/NYC), circa 1981-1983; 1 box (partial)
    - Nieves Falcón, Luis, circa 1980s-2013; 1 box (partial)
    - Northwestern University, 2006; 1 box (partial)
    - Noya, Elsa, circa 1997; 1 box (partial)
    - Noya, Vanessa, circa 1990-2001; 1 box (partial)
    - Odgen, Estrella, 1994; 1 box (partial)
    - Olivera, Eddie, 2015; 1 box (partial)
    - Oodally, Rumi, 2005; 1 box (partial)
    - Operation Bootstrap documentary film, undated; 1 box (partial)
    - Ortega, Eliana, circa 1982-1983; 1 box (partial)
    - Otero, Roberto (Puerto Rico), circa 1984; 1 box (partial)
    - Pabón, Milton (para Comité Consulta UPR), 1985; 1 box (partial)
    - Pabón, Milton (Puerto Rico), 1985; 1 box (partial)
    - Pacheco, José Emilio, circa 1990s; 1 box (partial)
    - Padilla López, Raul (Premio Juan Rulfo), 1998; 1 box (partial)
    - Parrilla, Eduardo, 1987; 1 box (partial)
    - Pastor, Beatriz, 1989; 1 box (partial)
    - Pautz, Patrick (Princeton), 1995; 1 box (partial)
    - Paz, Octavio (presentation/Princeton), undated; 1 box (partial)
    - Pérez, Lisandro, 1999; 1 box (partial)
    - Perez, Louis, undated; 1 box (partial)
    - Pérez-del-Solar, Pedro, 2004; 1 box (partial)
    - Pérez Meléndez, José Juan, circa 2003-2004; 1 box (partial)
    - Pérez Montero, José (Oviedo), circa 1960s; 1 box (partial)
    - Pérez-Stable, Marifeli, circa 1990s; 1 box (partial)
    - Perivolaris, John, circa 1995-1998; 1 box (partial)
    - Phaf, Ineke, 1986; 1 box (partial)
    - Philippi, Gretchen (Puerto Rico), 2006-2007; 1 box (partial)
    - Picó, Fernando, 1986; 1 box (partial)
    - Piglia, Ricardo, circa 1970s-2014; 1 box (partial)
    - Piglia, Ricardo - Defensa (Plata Quemada), undated; 1 box (partial)
    - Piglia, Ricardo (email correspondence copies), 1999-2007, 2011-2016; 1 box (partial)
    - Pineda Barnet, Enrique, circa 1992; 1 box (partial)
    - Pitol, Sergio - México (Premio Juan Rulfo), 1999; 1 box (partial)
    - Pont, Carmen Ana, 2005; 1 box (partial)
    - Pontious, Daniel, 1988-1989; 1 box (partial)
    - Pope, Randolph, circa 1982-1985; 1 box (partial)
    - Portes, Alejandro and Patricia Fernández, 1995; 1 box (partial)
    - Pozas Horcasitas, Ricardo, circa 1992, 2006; 1 box (partial)
    - Predmore, Michael, circa 1986-1992; 1 box (partial)
    - Price, Richard and Sally, 1992; 1 box (partial)
    - Princeton Alumni (in Puerto Rico), 2015; 1 box (partial)
    - Princeton University, circa 1980s-2010; 1 box (partial)
    - Princeton University Colloquium: Crossing Mexico, 2015; 1 box (partial)
    - Princeton University Colloquium: Post-colonial Theory, 2005; 1 box (partial)
    - Princeton University Diversity Committee, 1994; 1 box (partial)
    - Princeton University Humanities Council, 1990; 1 box (partial)
    - Princeton University (Puerto Rican Alumni), 1982-1983; 1 box (partial)
    - Princeton University (Romance Languages), 1989; 1 box (partial)
    - Princeton University Spanish Table, 1983; 1 box (partial)
    - Princeton University Third World Center, circa 1982-1984; 1 box (partial)
    - Princeton University - Universidad de Puerto Rico, 1981; 1 box (partial)
    - Program in Latin American Studies (PLAS), circa 1980s-1990s; 1 box (partial)
    - Program in Latin American Studies - Boletin, 1993, 1998, 2007; 1 box (partial)
    - Program in Latin American Studies - Colloquium: Intellectuals, 2007; 1 box (partial)
    - Program in Latin American Studies - Gerardo Gandini, undated; 1 box (partial)
    - Program in Latin American Studies - History, circa 1989-1990, 2006; 1 box (partial)
    - Program in Latin American Studies - Literature & Nationalism, 1989; 1 box (partial)
    - Program in Latin American Studies - Newsletter, 2002; 1 box (partial)
    - Program in Latin American Studies - País Portátil III, undated; 1 box (partial)
    - Program in Latin American Studies - Presidential Conference, circa 1993; 1 box (partial)
    - Program in Latin American Studies - Symposium, 1998; 1 box (partial)
    - Program in Latin American Studies - Stanley Stein, 1967; 1 box (partial)
    - Program in Latin American Studies - Towards a New History of Latin American & Caribbean Intellectuals, 2007; 1 box (partial)
    - Puerto Rico Cursillo de Verano (Universidad de Puerto Rico), 1991; 1 box (partial)
    - Puerto Rico: Departamento de Educación, 2009; 1 box (partial)
    - Puerto Rico Migration Division, circa 1989; 1 box (partial)
    - Pulido Ritter, Luis, 1994; 1 box (partial)
    - Puigdollers, Carmen (Puerto Rico), circa 1993; 1 box (partial)
    - Purin, Segio, undated; 1 box (partial)
    - Quijano, Aníbal, circa 1985-1987; 1 box (partial)
    - Quijano, Nick (Puerto Rico), circa 2016; 1 box (partial)
    - Quijano, Raquel (Puerto Rico), 2018; 1 box (partial)
    - Quintero Rivera, Angel, circa 1977-2012; 1 box (partial)
    - Raboteau, Albert J., 1995; 1 box (partial)
    - Rafucci, Alicia (Puerto Rico), 1971; 1 box (partial)
    - Rama, Angel, circa 1974-1983; 1 box (partial)
    - Ramírez, Isabel, 2012; 1 box (partial)
    - Ramírez, Mari Carmen (Puerto Rico), 2018; 1 box (partial)
    - Ramírez, Sergio, circa 2004-2014; 1 box (partial)
    - Ramos, Julio, circa 1980s-1990s; 1 box (partial)
    - Ramos Collado, Lilliana, circa 1980-1982; 1 box (partial)
    - Ramos Mattei, Andrés, circa 1983-1986; 1 box (partial)
    - Ramos Otero, Manuel, circa 1988-1989; 1 box (partial)
    - Rampersad, Arnold, circa 1990-1991; 1 box (partial)
    - Reina, Pedro, 2002; 1 box (partial)
    - Reis, João José, circa 1993; 1 box (partial)
    - Requena, Aixa (Puerto Rico), circa 2004; 1 box (partial)
    - Resina, Joán Ramón, 1992; 1 box (partial)
    - Reyes, Ismael, 2010; 1 box (partial)
    - Reyes, Joaquín (Puerto Rico), circa 1993; 1 box (partial)
    - Rey, César, 2000; 1 box (partial)
    - Richard, Nelly, 1998; 1 box (partial)
    - Rigau, Jorge (Puerto Rico), circa 1988-1989; 1 box (partial)
    - Rigolot, François, 1996, 1999; 1 box (partial)
    - Rincón, Carlos, circa 1990s; 1 box (partial)
    - Ríos Avila, Rubén, circa 2001-2005; 1 box (partial)
    - Rivera, Marcia, 1983, 1995; 1 box (partial)
    - Rivera Pagán, Luis, 1981; 1 box (partial)
    - Rivera Ramos, Efrén (Puerto Rico), 2001; 1 box (partial)
    - Rivera Rosa, Rafael, 2017; 1 box (partial)
    - Roa de la Carrera, Cristián, undated; 1 box (partial)
    - Rockefeller Foundation, circa 1994; 1 box (partial)
    - Rodríguez, Augusto, circa 1978; 1 box (partial)
    - Rodríguez, Erika (Puerto Rico), 2019; 1 box (partial)
    - Rodríguez, Ileana, circa 1991-1993; 1 box (partial)
    - Rodríguez, Marléne, 1994-1995; 1 box (partial)
    - Rodríguez, Pedro Pablo (Cuba), 1995; 1 box (partial)
    - Rodríguez, Reina María, 2006; 1 box (partial)
    - Rodríguez Castro, Malena, circa 1998-2003; 1 box (partial)
    - Rodríguez Castro, María Elena (Puerto Rico), circa 1989; 1 box (partial)
    - Rodríguez de Laguna, Asela, 1981; 1 box (partial)
    - Rodríguez-Luis, Julio, 1995; 1 box (partial)
    - Rodríguez Martinó, Graciela, circa 1983; 1 box (partial)
    - Rojas, Rafael, 1994-1996, 2006; 1 box (partial)
    - Romero, Soledad (Puerto Rico), 2000; 1 box (partial)
    - Roque Delgado, Aurelio (Puerto Rico), circa 1974-1984; 1 box (partial)
    - Rosado, César, 2001; 1 box (partial)
    - Ross, Andrew, 1991; 1 box (partial)